[
    {
       "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 1? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "3.14",
      "options": [
        "3.14",
        "6.14",
        "1.64",
        "4.64"
      ]
    },
    {
       "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 17? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "907.46",
      "options": [
        "905.96",
        "908.96",
        "910.46",
        "907.46"
      ]
    },
    {
       "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 9? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "254.34",
      "options": [
        "254.34",
        "252.84",
        "255.84",
        "257.34"
      ]
    },
    {
       "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 27? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "2289.06",
      "options": [
        "2292.06",
        "2287.56",
        "2289.06",
        "2290.56"
      ]
    },
    {
       "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 25? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "1962.5",
      "options": [
        "1961.0",
        "1965.5",
        "1962.5",
        "1964.0"
      ]
    },
    {
       "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 26?  (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "2122.64",
      "options": [
        "2122.64",
        "2125.64",
        "2121.14",
        "2124.14"
      ]
    },
    {
       "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 18?  (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "1017.36",
      "options": [
        "1015.86",
        "1020.36",
        "1018.86",
        "1017.36"
      ]
    },
    {
       "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 13?  (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "530.66",
      "options": [
        "529.16",
        "532.16",
        "533.66",
        "530.66"
      ]
    },
    {
       "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 23?  (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "1661.06",
      "options": [
        "1664.06",
        "1662.56",
        "1661.06",
        "1659.56"
      ]
    },
    {
       "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 26?  (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "2122.64",
      "options": [
        "2125.64",
        "2121.14",
        "2124.14",
        "2122.64"
      ]
    }
]